reuters.tv 2019-06-26

# Reuters TV - Privacy

## SCOPE

Your privacy is important to Thomson Reuters. This Privacy Statement applies to the online collection and sharing of personal and other information via the Reuters TV application operated by Thomson Reuters and its worldwide affiliated companies and subsidiaries. This Statement does not apply to information collected in any other way, including offline, through Thomson Reuters websites, or through other Thomson Reuters applications. Reuters TV may contain links to or options for users to integrate with sites and services maintained by third parties such as Facebook, Twitter, and LinkedIn. These third party sites and services are not operated or managed by Thomson Reuters and we have no control over information, content, preferences, etc., you chose to submit to, share with or that is otherwise collected by them. As such, you should refer to those sites’ privacy statements for further information related to their privacy practices.

## DEFINITIONS

In this Privacy Statement

  * the terms "Personal Information" or "Personally Identifiable Information" means your name, address, phone number, email address, payment card information, and/or certain additional categories of information that identify you personally; and 
  * the terms "Personal Information" and "Personally Identifiable Information" do not include username, technical information (for example, Unique Device Identifier or "UDID," Media Access Control "MAC" address, Apple’s Identifier For Advertising or "IFA," and Internet Protocol or "IP" address), or numbers or alpha-numeric identifiers assigned by us, third-parties, or your computer. 

## PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

When you register for our services or order products via our site, we ask you to provide certain Personal Information such as your name, address, phone number, email address, payment card information. We keep this information in a contact database for future reference, as needed. We may use certain information you provide to offer you products and services that we believe may be of interest to you. If you don't wish to receive such offers, you may opt out (unsubscribe) as described in this Statement below. 

If you contact us for customer support, we may ask you to provide information about your computer/mobile device or about the issues you are trying to resolve. This information is necessary to help us answer your questions. We may record your requests and our responses for quality control purposes. 

We don't share any of the Personal Information you provide with others, unless we say so in this Privacy Statement, or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. 

## WHAT OTHER INFORMATION DOES THOMSON REUTERS COLLECT AND HOW DO WE USE IT?

We collect information about our users, including username, purchased content, network and device information, and usage data, in the following ways: directly from the user (for example, when ordering a product, registering an account, or signing up for a newsletter), from our web server & application logs, through cookies, beacons, and through the use of local storage, including but not limited to, through local shared objects or "flash cookies," as well as other files. The device or devices on which you use Reuters TV will determine, in part, the exact manner in which we collect or store information. 

We use the information primarily to provide you with a personalized experience that delivers the information, content, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you. 

### Web Server Logs

When you use the Reuters TV application, we will track information about your use of the application and store that information in web server logs. Our servers automatically capture and save the information electronically. Examples of the information we may collect include: 

  * Your Internet protocol address 
  * A unique identifier we assign to your device (or a unique identifier already associated with your device) 
  * UDID, MAC address, IFA, or similar identifiers 
  * Information or text that you enter in the application 
  * The name of your Internet service provider 
  * Other technical facts regarding your network access 
  * The city, state, and country where you are using the application 
  * The kind of operating system and device you use, including version number 
  * Other technical facts regarding your device 
  * Language preferences 
  * The number of links or buttons you click within the application 
  * The date and time of your visit 
  * The content you viewed, purchased, or stored 
  * Certain searches/queries that you conducted via the application 

The information we collect in web server logs helps us administer the applications, analyze their usage, protect the application and its content from inappropriate use, and improve the user's experience. 

### Local Storage (cookies and other technologies)

If you use Reuters TV on a mobile device, we will also store information locally on the device regarding the content that you purchase, access, and view, as well as your username. This information is stored in order to help the application work. This information is deleted from your device when you delete the application. However, unique identifiers that are persistently associated with your device, including UDID, MAC address, or unique identifiers derived from your device’s technical information, will remain the same after deletion of the Reuters TV application. 

### Third Party Services

We may use services hosted by third parties to assist in providing our services and to help us understand our customers’ use of our products. These services may collect information sent by your device when you use the application, including IP address, type of device, operating system version, unique or persistent identifiers associated with your device (such as UDID, MAC address, IFA, or identifiers derived from your device’s technical information), network information, technical characteristics of your device or its software, language settings, and usage information relating to your use of the application. If and when these third party services collect information, they do so without collecting Personal Information. 

## HOW DOES THOMSON REUTERS PROTECT THE PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT IT COLLECTS?

We have implemented certain appropriate security measures to help protect your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, some of your network communications when you use Reuters TV are protected with Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology which protects against eavesdroppers by using encryption. Also, we store Personal Information in a data center with restricted access and appropriate monitoring, and we use a variety of technical security measures to secure your data. In addition, we use intrusion detection and virus protection software. **However, please note that we do not guarantee that unauthorized persons will always be unable to defeat our security measures.**

Also, please note that we may store and process your personal information in systems located outside of your home country, including countries located outside of the European Union. However, regardless of where storage and processing may occur, we take appropriate steps to ensure that your information is protected, consistent with the principles set forth under this statement. By using this application you consent to your information being collected, used and transferred as described in this privacy statement. 

## WHO HAS ACCESS TO THE PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We will not sell, rent, or lease mailing lists or your Personal Information to others, and we will not make your Personal Information available to any unaffiliated parties, except as follows:

  * To agents and/or contractors who may use it on our behalf or in connection with their relationship with us (for example, we may use third parties to help us with promotional campaigns). 
  * As required by law, in a matter of public safety or policy, as needed in connection with the transfer of our business assets (for example, if we are acquired by another company or if we are liquidated during bankruptcy proceedings), or if we believe in good faith that sharing the data is necessary to protect our rights or property. 

We also rely on some of our affiliates for support of the products and services we offer, and we share some of our back-office functions with other Thomson Reuters companies. Our affiliates are all required to preserve the confidentiality of any personal information they may access. 

We will not disclose your Personal Information to unaffiliated third parties, except as necessary to service the account, to enforce the terms of use, to meet our obligations to content and technology providers, or as required by law. 

We may also use statistics regarding usage for product development purposes, but we only use those statistics in the aggregate and they don't include any Personal Information. 

Your access to some of our services and content may be password protected, such as via OnePass. We recommend that you refrain from disclosing your username(s) and password(s) to anyone. We also recommend that you sign out of your account or service at the end of each session. You may also wish to close your browser window when you have finished your work, especially if you share a computer with someone else or if you are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe. 

## HOW MAY I CORRECT, AMEND, OR DELETE MY PERSONAL INFORMATION, OR UPDATE MY PREFERENCES?

You may cancel your registration or update your preferences at any time. If you don't want to receive information about our products or services, please update your account preferences (where available), check the appropriate box when registering, and/or utilize the "unsubscribe" mechanism within the communications that you receive from us. 

* * *

## QUESTIONS?

If you have any questions or concerns related to this statement and/or our practices, please contact us using the "contact us" link in the application, email us at [ReutersTV_support@reuters.com](mailto:ReutersTV_support@reuters.com) or write to us at at:

**Thomson Reuters**  
3 Times Square  
New York, NY 10036  

## PRIVACY STATEMENT CHANGES

Our Privacy Statement may change at any time. If our information practices change in a significant way, we will post the policy changes here. This Privacy Statement was last updated on October 7th 2014.
